<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Schrodin&#39;s Diary on Quantum Computing and Quantum Programming</title>
    <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Schrodin&#39;s Diary on Quantum Computing and Quantum Programming</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>english</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:50:26 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://schrodinteq.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Machine Learning on AWS Amazon Braket: QCBM</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/awsquantummachinelearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:50:26 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/awsquantummachinelearning/</guid>
      <description>As described in another article, Amazon Braket, AWS’s quantum computing service, allows users to easily access various features through the Amazon Braket SDK, a software development kit for quantum computing. In this article, we explain how to run quantum machine learning algorithms—machine learning techniques that leverage quantum computers.&#xA;Amazon Braket Learning Course You can efficiently learn the basic knowledge of quantum computing—including quantum gates and quantum circuits introduced in this article—as well as how to use Amazon Braket through this course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About the error when importing the Amazon Braket algorithm library.</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/braketexperimenterror/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 21:19:07 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/braketexperimenterror/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Braket Learning Course I have created a learning course on Amazon Braket, AWS&amp;rsquo;s quantum computing service.&#xA;https://www.udemy.com/course/quantum-computing-on-aws-for-beginners-amazon-braket/?referralCode=F361C3FD774489A1B5B8 This course is designed for those with no prior knowledge of quantum computing or AWS, and by the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll even be able to learn about quantum machine learning. Take advantage of this opportunity to build your skills in quantum technologies!&#xA;Error when importing braket.experimental As already introduced in another article, Amazon Braket allows you to easily run algorithms such as Quantum Fourier Transform and quantum machine learning using its algorithm library.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install the Amazon Braket SDK and run quantum circuits in Jupyter Notebook.&#34;</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/installrunbraketsdk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 17:47:23 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/installrunbraketsdk/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to install the Amazon Braket SDK, a quantum computing SDK provided by AWS, and run it on Jupyter Notebook.&#xA;Amazon Braket Learning Course For those who want to learn more about Amazon Braket mentioned in this article, here is an introduction to the Amazon Braket learning course.&#xA;https://www.udemy.com/course/quantum-computing-on-aws-for-beginners-amazon-braket/?referralCode=F361C3FD774489A1B5B8 This course is designed for those with no prior knowledge of quantum computing or AWS, and by the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll even be able to learn about quantum machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Qiskit 2.0 and run a simple quantum circuit.</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/qiskit20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:01:51 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/qiskit20/</guid>
      <description>Qiskit 2.0 has been released. In this article, we will explain how to run a simple quantum circuit using Qiskit 2.0.1.&#xA;Amazon Braket Learning Course I have created a learning course on Amazon Braket, AWS&amp;rsquo;s quantum computing service.&#xA;https://www.udemy.com/course/quantum-computing-on-aws-for-beginners-amazon-braket/?referralCode=F361C3FD774489A1B5B8 This course is designed for those with no prior knowledge of quantum computing or AWS, and by the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll even be able to learn about quantum machine learning. Take advantage of this opportunity to build your skills in quantum technologies!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Qiskit on Amazon Braket</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/awsbraketqiskit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:40:23 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/awsbraketqiskit/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to use Qiskit from an Amazon Braket notebook, one of the quantum computing services provided by AWS.&#xA;Amazon Braket Learning Course I have created a learning course on Amazon Braket, AWS&amp;rsquo;s quantum computing service.&#xA;https://www.udemy.com/course/quantum-computing-on-aws-for-beginners-amazon-braket/?referralCode=F361C3FD774489A1B5B8 This course is designed for those with no prior knowledge of quantum computing or AWS, and by the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll even be able to learn about quantum machine learning. Take advantage of this opportunity to build your skills in quantum technologies!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AccessDeniedException in Amazon Braket</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/braketexrole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:34:09 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/braketexrole/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Braket Learning Course I have created a learning course on Amazon Braket, AWS&amp;rsquo;s quantum computing service.&#xA;https://www.udemy.com/course/quantum-computing-on-aws-for-beginners-amazon-braket/?referralCode=F361C3FD774489A1B5B8 This course is designed for those with no prior knowledge of quantum computing or AWS, and by the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll even be able to learn about quantum machine learning. Take advantage of this opportunity to build your skills in quantum technologies!&#xA;AccessDeniedException in Amazon Braket When attempting to run the SV1, TN1, DM1 simulators or quantum computers on Amazon Braket, the following error may be encountered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error due to insufficient memory in Amazon Braket</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/braketmemerr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:07:44 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/braketmemerr/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Braket Learning Course I have created a learning course on Amazon Braket, AWS&amp;rsquo;s quantum computing service.&#xA;https://www.udemy.com/course/quantum-computing-on-aws-for-beginners-amazon-braket/?referralCode=F361C3FD774489A1B5B8 This course is designed for those with no prior knowledge of quantum computing or AWS, and by the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll even be able to learn about quantum machine learning. Take advantage of this opportunity to build your skills in quantum technologies!&#xA;Error Due to Insufficient Memory in Amazon Braket Local Simulator When running the local simulator in Amazon Braket, AWS&amp;rsquo;s quantum computing service, the following error may be output.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Amazon Braket?</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/whatisamazonbraket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:15:01 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/whatisamazonbraket/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I will explain the overview of Amazon Braket, a quantum computing service provided by AWS, while also mentioning the personal benefits I feel.&#xA;Amazon Braket Learning Course I have created a learning course on Amazon Braket, AWS&amp;rsquo;s quantum computing service.&#xA;https://www.udemy.com/course/quantum-computing-on-aws-for-beginners-amazon-braket/?referralCode=F361C3FD774489A1B5B8 This course is designed for those with no prior knowledge of quantum computing or AWS, and by the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll even be able to learn about quantum machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run any desired version of Qiskit using a Python virtual environment.</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/venv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:11:19 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/venv/</guid>
      <description>Regarding the IBM Quantum Developer Certification Exam IBM offers a certification exam related to Qiskit, which is introduced in this blog.&#xA;By obtaining this certification, you can prove your knowledge of Qiskit and quantum programming. For those aiming to achieve this certification, I have created a practice exams on the Udemy platform! I have made the explanations as clear as possible, so please make sure to take full advantage of the following practice exams as extra study material for exam preparation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Quantum Developer Certification Sample Test Explanation Part 2</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/ibmcertsample02en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 20:55:42 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/ibmcertsample02en/</guid>
      <description>To earn the certification &amp;ldquo;IBM Certified Associate Developer - Quantum Computation using Qiskit v0.2X&amp;rdquo; provided by IBM, you need to pass the exam &amp;ldquo;Exam C1000-112: Fundamentals of Quantum Computation Using Qiskit v0.2X Developer.&amp;rdquo; In the URL below, which contains an overview of the exam, there is a link to a sample question set.&#xA;https://www.ibm.com/training/certification/ibm-certified-associate-developer-quantum-computation-using-qiskit-v02x-C0010300&#xA;I have provided explanations for questions 1 to 10 of the sample question set on the previous page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Quantum Developer Certification Sample Test Explanation Part 1</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/ibmcertsample01en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:32:53 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/ibmcertsample01en/</guid>
      <description>In the other page, it was mentioned that, unlike classical computers, quantum computers require quantum programs to be implemented. IBM has been offering a certification related to quantum programming called &amp;lsquo;IBM Certified Associate Developer - Quantum Computation using Qiskit v0.2X&amp;rsquo; since 2021.&#xA;https://www.ibm.com/training/certification/ibm-certified-associate-developer-quantum-computation-using-qiskit-v02x-C0010300&#xA;By obtaining this certification, you can demonstrate your knowledge of Qiskit and quantum programming!&#xA;To earn this certification, you need to pass the exam titled &amp;ldquo;Exam C1000-112: Fundamentals of Quantum Computation Using Qiskit v0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum computers and quantum programming: What are they?</title>
      <link>https://schrodinteq.github.io/c2q01en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 20:53:18 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://schrodinteq.github.io/c2q01en/</guid>
      <description>Classical Computers vs Quantum Computers Quantum computers, which have been gaining increased attention in recent years, differ from the computers we use in our daily lives. What is the fundamental difference?&#xA;The most significant and fundamental difference lies in the bit. Let&amp;rsquo;s refer to the computers we use daily as classical computers. In classical computers, processing is done by assigning each bit a value of either 0 or 1. When discussing quantum computers, the bits used in classical computers are often called classical bits.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
